{
  "title": "Compound words: aftermath, afterthought, afterbirth",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "After experiencing too many late ........ "Sinking spells", The Duchess of Bedford arrived upon the idea of having tea and finger food at about 5 p.m. ",
      "answers": ["afterwards", "afterbirth", "afternoon", "aftertaste"],
      "correct": "afternoon"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "In the ........ of World War I the political, cultural, and social order of the world was drastically changed in many places, even outside the areas directly involved in the war. ",
      "answers": ["afterwards", "afterbirth", "afternoon", "aftermath"],
      "correct": "aftermath"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "I'm not convinced that the Christian ........ would mean much to me if I had to lie and cheat in order to attain it. ",
      "answers": ["afternoon", "aftertaste", "afterlife", "afterbirth"],
      "correct": "afterlife"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "It is better to halt mass murder than to clean it up ........ ",
      "answers": ["afterthought", "aftermath", "afterwards", "afterlife"],
      "correct": "afterwards"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "The ........ is delivered during the third stage of labour. ",
      "answers": ["afterthought", "afterlife", "aftertaste", "afterbirth"],
      "correct": "afterbirth"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "The fruity tones of this mild balanced brew produce a delightful ........ ",
      "answers": ["afterthought", "afternoon", "aftertaste", "afterlife"],
      "correct": "aftertaste"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Contrary to popular opinion, Judaism does believe in an ....... , but it is not the primary focus of the religion. ",
      "answers": ["afterthought", "afternoon", "aftertaste", "afterlife"],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "We enjoyed the rest of our lunch ....... , but I think we were both pretty taken aback by the encounter we had when we first entered the restaurant. ",
      "answers": ["afterwards", "aftermath", "afternoon", "aftertaste"],
      "correct": "afterwards"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Childcare is currently available for kindergarten children on a Tuesday and a Thursday ........ from 1.00 p.m. to 3.00 p.m. ",
      "answers": ["afterthought", "afternoon", "aftertaste", "afterbirth"],
      "correct": "afternoon"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "The Emergency Response and Transitional Recovery Programme commenced activities in January 2005 in the immediate ........ of the Tsunami disaster of 26 December 2004. ",
      "answers": ["afterthought", "aftertaste", "afternoon", "aftermath"],
      "correct": "aftermath"
    }
  ]
}
